{
    "subject": "Pierce_Brosnan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Keely_Shaye_Smith",
    "human_readable": "Pierce Brosnan is married to Keely Shaye Smith.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9774500131607056,
            "question": "Is there a known relationship between Pierce Brosnan and Keely Shaye Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9761649370193481,
            "question": "Are Pierce Brosnan and Keely Shaye Smith a couple?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.947799563407898,
            "question": "To whom is Keely Shaye Smith married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9473861455917358,
            "question": "Who is married to Keely Shaye Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9140723943710327,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the relationship between Pierce Brosnan and Keely Shaye Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8824583888053894,
            "question": "Is Pierce Brosnan currently married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.75547194480896,
            "question": "Who is Pierce Brosnan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7430926561355591,
            "question": "Who is Keely Shaye Smith?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.740080714225769,
            "question": "What is the name of Pierce Brosnan's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6591112017631531,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Pierce Brosnan?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Pierce Brosnan is married to Keely Shaye Smith.",
            "html": "yago_23089_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Pierce Brosnan's wife?",
            "html": "yago_23089_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Keely Shaye Smith?",
            "html": "yago_23089_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Pierce Brosnan?",
            "html": "yago_23089_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_101.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23089_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The information in the documents indeed supports the triple.\n\nHere's the structured JSON format response:\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention Pierce Brosnan being married to Keely Shaye Smith on multiple occasions (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23089/re-ranker-msmarco/13.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_23089/re-ranker-msmarco/64.txt, etc.), which confirms that the triple is correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Pierce Brosnan has been married to Keely Shaye Smith for 23 years, and provide details about their wedding anniversary celebrations. Therefore, the statement \"Pierce Brosnan is married to Keely Shaye Smith\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}